One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
Th...
Th-This can't be happening!
CP9's leader, Mr. Rob Lucci, is considered to be the most powerful agent...
in the history of Cipher Pol.
Utter Defeat
His defeat at the hands of a mere pirate is unbelievable!
Luffy won!
He had me on pins and needles there.
So you finally did it, Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Everyone, hurry to the ship!
We're gonna set sail!
You did it! Luffy!
You did it, Straw Hat!
Y-You morons! The Navy will hear us!
That's okay! Let them hear!
Hey! Who's saying that?!
Unknown! They're transmitting
via transponder snail!
Big Bro!
What is this voice?!
Shut yer mouth! If only we'd taken off,
the Navy would've thought we died!
You guys!
Those guys!
What's the likelihood they're the same pirates
we eliminated at the main gate?
Well, I don't see how.
I'm sure they all fell off the cliff!
There's no way they could've survived.
Dammit! It's cannon fire!
Big Bro!
Hey, idiot! Don't push!
Don't move!
We're gonna fall!
The ropes are gonna rip!
You morons! Galley-La's ropes never break!
Sheesh, I already toldya to keep yer mouth shut.
We're all okay!
The giants blocked us from the cannon fire!
Whoa! They're undeniably tenacious.
Grandma! They're all alive!
Sodom and Gomorrah are gonna make it too!
I'm so glad to hear that!
But if we stick around here,
the battleships are sure to come back.
Let's get the hell outta here!
Oh, and we have a means of escape,
so don't worry about us!
Let's meet up after we get out alive!
That's right!
Let's hurry!
You guys gonna climb, or what?
The blood is rushing up to my head!
No, it's rushing down!
Okay, climb up!
Climb up slowly!
We're gonna fall!
Don't shake!
You stupid... jerks!
You guys think I was worried? You dumbasses!
Those numbskulls are alive!
I... I couldn't be happier! What a relief!
Yeah. No denying it's a relief,
but it'd be a waste if you died here, right?
Yeah. You're right.
Should we head over to the main gate right away?!
Later. For now, we should focus our efforts here.
What're you all doing?!
Carry out your orders already!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Bring on as many guys as you've got!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Tiger Trap!
Oni Giri!
Pound Phoenix!
Cien Fleur!
Keep an eye on Straw Hat in the first column!
Y-Yes, sir, but...
Hm?
The pirate Straw Hat Luffy
appears to be severely wounded!
He isn't moving at all!
What?!
Hey, Luffy!
What're you doing?!
Hurry and get your butt over here!
We're as good as dead if we stay here!
What's gotten into you?! We're so close!
Use your Rubber Rubber and shoot yourself over here!
I'll carry you the rest of the way!
We're surrounded by the sea
and a bunch of battleships!
If we stay here, we're goners!
It seems that the pirates are trying
to escape aboard the escort ship.
Yeah.
Luffy!
I-I can't.
My body.
What?
It won't move at all.
It won't move?
Don't be ridiculous! You defeated the enemy!
Robin's back too!
All we need to do now is leave!
Please! Give it your all!
Usopp!
We're gonna take the ship over to Luffy's column.
Everyone! Hurry aboard!
Fire!
No! Our escape ship!
Oh, crap! Now it's hopeless.
That ship was our only way outta here!
Kokoro-san... Chimney... Gonbe... Chopper!
O-Oh no.
They survived somehow!
Outta the way!
Thank goodness!
Sanji-kun! Where in the world have you been?!
Sorry about that.
I had to take care of something.
At any rate, we're in serious trouble here.
Since getting back Robin-chan,
I thought this area would be safe from attack. But the ship–
This is as far as you go!
Release the old lady now and–
Don't waste our time!
Mermaid Kick!
Fire.
Now they're firing on their own people!
Cut them off at the second column!
Fire!
Watch out! Run! Run!
Dammit! Looks like they demolished the entire bridge.
We're stuck on this column!
We're out of options!
No choice but to fight them all here and now!
Are you nuts?! Each new wave of enemies is gonna be stronger than the last!
Ready all cannons to fire on the first column!
Eliminate Straw Hat Luffy immediately!
Luffy!
Luffy's in danger!
We need to at least get him over here!
Oh, crap!
Luffy!
It won't work. At this distance,
even if I try to pull him, I'll drop him into the sea.
Luffy!
This is bad. They're in a real pickle!
Straw Hat won, but he can't stand up!
It seems like his life is in danger!
What?!
Straw Hat!
Stand up, Straw Hat!
Pull it together, kid!
Pirate guy!
Luffy! Stand up! Please!
Isn't there something you can do, Luffy?!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! You can do it!
Oh, crap. I'm in serious trouble!
Again?
Who is that?!
Hey! Are you tryna get killed?!
This is no time to be spacing out!
Just whose voice is this?
Th-That's right! It's the same voice from before.
What does this mean?!
Straw Hat!
It's obvious! It's my minions!
No! Not those voices!
I've been hearing it for a while!
Huh?!
Below?
Look below?
Yeah, I do hear it. What? Below?
Who's that?!
What the hell is this?
It's telling us to look below!
What're you talking about, reindeer-chan?
Ready the guns to fire at Straw Hat Luffy in the first column in five seconds!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
Jump into the sea!
Four seconds!
Into the sea!
Usopp?!
Robin, can you drop Luffy into the sea?
Leave it to me!
You idiot! Are you trying to get us to kill ourselves?!
Something so drastic won't save us!
Three!
We're gonna be saved! She came to rescue us!
We've got one more friend, remember?!
Two!
Chopper! Did you look below?!
I did!
Cien Fleur:
One!
Delphinium!
I'm moving! Is Robin doing this?!
Into the sea!
Follow Luffy!
Here we go!
Into the sea!
The pirates are jumping into the sea!
How stupid! There's no surviving these waters.
Are they out of their minds?!
Everyone, let's go back!
Fire!
Back to the seas of adventure!
Jump on the Merry!
Merry!
I came to get you!
What're they trying to pull?!
Jumping into the sea is the last thing they should do!
A few of them are also ability users!
That's suicide!
Hey, hold on a sec.
What the heck is that?
It's a ship! Judging by the Jolly Roger,
it's the Straw Hat Pirates' ship!
How did it sneak past all our battleships undetected?
I don't know who you are, but thanks...
What the heck?
Is something wrong, Sanji-kun?
Hmm. Well, Nami-san,
while the rope ladder definitely lowered,
there doesn't look to be anyone here.
What?!
Yay!
Seriously. Learn how to swim, brother!
Now, get on board, all of you with powers!
Robin-chwan!
Come fly into my arms!
This is the Merry! It's the Merry!
I really love the Merry!
Merry. Merry!
My Merry is alive!
W-Why are you so...
I-If I could... If only I could do more!
I can't believe it!
This ship plummeted into the sea.
Who could have sailed the ship here?
We'll talk about it later!
Give us your instructions!
You're right.
Let's get out of here!
Hey! What're you doing, Sanji-kun?!
N-Nami-swan!
That was close!
I thought those battleships were gonna kill me!
Hey, Robin! You saved me! Thank y–
Just leave the rest to us!
Luffy... and everyone,
thank you!
Don't worry about it.
You can say stupid stuff like that once we escape.
What do you mean "stupid stuff," you damn Moss Head?!
What do you mean, you damn Moss Head?!
Shut up! If we die here,
none of this'll mean a damn thing!
Apologize to Robin-chan, you bastard!
He's right! Apologize to Robin!
Give it a rest!
Hm? Hey, Chopper!
You can move now?
What?
Y-You're right! I'm moving!
I can move now, Zoro!
Apologize to Robin already!
Give up yet?
No! No!
C'mon, guys! Let's hurry and get outta here!
Yeah!
Hey, hey! This is unacceptable!
Are you guys just letting them get away?!
If they're going to escape,
might as well blow up Nico Robin after all!
But we have to capture her alive!
This is coming straight from Admiral Aokiji.
All ships! Prepare to fire!
F-From A-Admiral Aokiji?!
Okay! Aim at them!
All ships! Ready the guns to fire!
They fell for it.
I can't let them get away. They need to die.
I'll just kill 'em all!
Hey! Get the lead out and load the cannonballs!
So Spandam is alive.
They're gonna fire at us!
Catch the wind from starboard and head east!
We can't! We're completely surrounded!
There're just too many cannons!
They'll hit the ship for sure!
Fire!
Ahh! Here it comes!
Hey, did those misfire?
None of their other attacks are hitting us either!
Just where do you think you're all aiming?!
There's something wrong!
It's like the cannons are aiming themselves!
Don't give me a half-baked excuse!
Stay clear!
We can't! We're gonna collide!
It's coming this way! What the hell is going on?!
What's going on?! Give me a report!
L-Look over there!
What the hell?!
The Gates of Justice suddenly began to close.
Currents normally blocked
by the gates are producing whirlpools,
and we've lost control of the rudder!
So that explains our imprecise aim!
Don't get swept up by the currents!
Wh-What the hell is going on?
Put out that fire! On the double!
This is too much! Everyone, get out of here!
Idiots! Why did you close the gates?
What did you morons think would happen?!
The lever for the gates is
in the third column of the Bridge of Hesitation,
so we couldn't have touched it!
Whoa! This is better than I expected!
Sanji! Don't tell me you did something earlier!
Yep.
Guts alone won't let us escape this kind of foe. Right?
Bingo!
Th-That's amazing, Sanji!
Are you some kind of genius?!
I hate to cut the celebrations short,
but the whirlpools are a problem for us too.
Ahh! That's right! We're–
Shut up, you guys!
There wasn't a sea the Merry
couldn't cross with us on board!
Ohhh!
Nami-san! You're so cool!
That's right! We're counting on you, navigator!
Just hold them off until I figure out
the trajectory of the whirlpools!
Leave it to us!
One-Sword Style: 36-Pound Phoenix!
Dammit! Why?! Why can't you bring down
one puny little ship with seven battleships?!
You useless morons!
Hey, they're coming your way, Usopp!
Okay! Leave them to me!
I missed one! Sanji, take care of it!
Basse Côte!
Ahhh! I'm gonna fight too!
You idiot! You can't move, can you?!
He's right, Luffy. Leave this one to us...
and take it easy!
Ahhh! I don't care what you guys say;
I'm gonna fight!
I'll give a medal to the one
who actually hits them! So hurry up and hit them!
All ships! Concentrate cannons on their ship's aft deck.
Fire!
Don't talk back! I'm your captain!
Whoa!
One...
Two...
Three!
Not good! They're bouncing back our way!
That saved us, Captain!
Just what we'd expect from you, Captain!
Hey! Are you guys demons?!
Victory!
I see it... the way to victory!
Chopper, hard aport at 9 o'clock!
O-Okay!
The pirate ship escaped toward the falls!
Fire! Fire! What're you doing?!
Are you all idiots?! Sink that ship already!
It seems they're using
the natural flow of the whirlpools!
Their speed is ludicrous!
I'm gonna be useful too!
Go for it, reindeer-chan!
Go! Full speed ahead!
Dammit! Dammit! Those bastards!
With the entire military force
of Enies Lobby at our disposal...
With the power of the buster call,
as strong as an entire country's military...
Why... Why in the hell can't we...
Why? Why can't we take a single woman...
from a puny little band of pirates?!
Chief!
Help!
Help.
Clutch!
C-Chief!
Let's go, pirates! Let's go!
All right, it's about time.
Franky,
could you do that thing?!
Got it!
Everyone, brace yourselves.
Block their route! The enemy ship
can't get out of the whirlpools!
This'll be rough on the ship. Sorry about that.
Coup de Vent!
Th-The pirate ship is flying!
Is this really happening?!
They've gone outside the fleet's range!
Don't underestimate what she's been through!
The Merry flew 10,000 meters high in the sky!
Lethal Super Smoke Star!
It's a smokescreen!
Those bastards!
After them! We bow to nobody in speed!
We can't! We're caught in the whirlpools!
It's taking everything we've got just to stay afloat!
Fire! Fire!
It seems that Straw Hat and
the others were able to escape!
All right! We'll head back too!
Go, Puffing Tom!
We'll still pursue them.
We can't possibly let it end like this.
To maintain our dignity as the Navy—
no, as the World Government—
we'll bring down the Straw Hat Pirates,
and we'll capture Nico Robin,
the most dangerous criminal, without fail!
Therefore, we require fleet reinforcements and additional marines–
Don't bother.
But–
We used a buster call,
an attack as strong as entire nations.
When you look at the blunder
this fleet made and the current state...
of Enies Lobby, the very symbol of law,
it's quite apparent.
This battle ends in our utter defeat.
Is the top of this ram's head here okay?
Yep. That's my seat.
There you go. Be careful not to fall.
Yeah. Thanks, old monster lady.
Thanks, Merry.
Thanks to you, we were able to escape.
I never would've imagined that you'd come, Merry.
But when I think about it,
you've always protected us.
I'm so glad that you're our friend.
Thanks, Merry!
At any rate,
you guys sure did pull one outrageous stunt back there.
To start with, who would've guessed that
you'd shoot the World Government's flag!
Well, it's not a big deal.
All we did was take back a friend
who was taken from us.
Thanks for helping us save Robin.
Well, y'know, it was no big deal.
Anyway,
we claim...
this fight...
as a win!
Yeah!